[
    {
        "question": "Who is the main protagonist of *Naruto*?",
        "options": [
            "Naruto Uzumaki",
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Sakura Haruno",
            "Kakashi Hatake"
        ],
        "answer": "Naruto Uzumaki"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Naruto’s dream throughout the series?",
        "options": [
            "To become Hokage",
            "To find his parents",
            "To defeat Sasuke",
            "To master all jutsu"
        ],
        "answer": "To become Hokage"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which clan does Sasuke Uchiha belong to?",
        "options": [
            "Uchiha Clan",
            "Hyuga Clan",
            "Nara Clan",
            "Akimichi Clan"
        ],
        "answer": "Uchiha Clan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the leader of the Akatsuki organization?",
        "options": [
            "Pain",
            "Orochimaru",
            "Itachi Uchiha",
            "Madara Uchiha"
        ],
        "answer": "Pain"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Naruto’s signature technique?",
        "options": [
            "Shadow Clone Jutsu",
            "Rasengan",
            "Chidori",
            "Kage Bunshin no Jutsu"
        ],
        "answer": "Shadow Clone Jutsu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Naruto’s mentor and the leader of Team 7?",
        "options": [
            "Kakashi Hatake",
            "Jiraiya",
            "Orochimaru",
            "Minato Namikaze"
        ],
        "answer": "Kakashi Hatake"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Nine-Tailed Fox sealed inside Naruto?",
        "options": [
            "Kurama",
            "Shukaku",
            "Gyuki",
            "Kokuo"
        ],
        "answer": "Kurama"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Fourth Hokage?",
        "options": [
            "Minato Namikaze",
            "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
            "Tobirama Senju",
            "Hashirama Senju"
        ],
        "answer": "Minato Namikaze"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Sasuke’s older brother?",
        "options": [
            "Itachi Uchiha",
            "Madara Uchiha",
            "Obito Uchiha",
            "Kakashi Hatake"
        ],
        "answer": "Itachi Uchiha"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Sakura Haruno’s primary ability?",
        "options": [
            "Superhuman Strength",
            "Rasengan",
            "Sharingan",
            "Byakugan"
        ],
        "answer": "Superhuman Strength"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which village does Naruto belong to?",
        "options": [
            "Konoha",
            "Suna",
            "Kiri",
            "Iwa"
        ],
        "answer": "Konoha"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the technique that allows the user to control and manipulate chakra into a sphere?",
        "options": [
            "Rasengan",
            "Chidori",
            "Kage Bunshin",
            "Hiraishin"
        ],
        "answer": "Rasengan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is known as the 'Copy Ninja'?",
        "options": [
            "Kakashi Hatake",
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Naruto Uzumaki",
            "Orochimaru"
        ],
        "answer": "Kakashi Hatake"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which member of Team 7 is a master of lightning-based techniques?",
        "options": [
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Naruto Uzumaki",
            "Sakura Haruno",
            "Kakashi Hatake"
        ],
        "answer": "Sasuke Uchiha"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the technique used to create clones that are solid and can perform jutsu?",
        "options": [
            "Shadow Clone Jutsu",
            "Basic Clone Jutsu",
            "Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu",
            "Transformation Jutsu"
        ],
        "answer": "Shadow Clone Jutsu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the organization that seeks to capture all of the Tailed Beasts?",
        "options": [
            "Akatsuki",
            "Root",
            "Orochimaru’s Group",
            "The Twelve Guardians"
        ],
        "answer": "Akatsuki"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the host of the Eight-Tails, Gyuki?",
        "options": [
            "Killer Bee",
            "Naruto Uzumaki",
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Might Guy"
        ],
        "answer": "Killer Bee"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the technique used by Naruto that combines the Rasengan with his Shadow Clones?",
        "options": [
            "Rasenshuriken",
            "Rasengan",
            "Chidori",
            "Kage Bunshin"
        ],
        "answer": "Rasenshuriken"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the leader of the Sannin alongside Jiraiya and Orochimaru?",
        "options": [
            "Tsunade",
            "Sakura Haruno",
            "Kurenai Yuhi",
            "Anko Mitarashi"
        ],
        "answer": "Tsunade"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is known for his unique ability to manipulate sand?",
        "options": [
            "Gaara",
            "Kankuro",
            "Temari",
            "Sasori"
        ],
        "answer": "Gaara"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the secret organization that operates within the village of Konoha, led by Danzo Shimura?",
        "options": [
            "Root",
            "Anbu",
            "Akatsuki",
            "Twelve Guardian Ninja"
        ],
        "answer": "Root"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the character that has the ability to manipulate wood and is known as the 'God of Shinobi'?",
        "options": [
            "Hashirama Senju",
            "Tobirama Senju",
            "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
            "Minato Namikaze"
        ],
        "answer": "Hashirama Senju"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the powerful ability that grants the user precognitive abilities and is also known as the 'Third Eye'?",
        "options": [
            "Rinnegan",
            "Sharingan",
            "Byakugan",
            "Kekkei Genkai"
        ],
        "answer": "Rinnegan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the village that is known for its expertise in medical ninjutsu?",
        "options": [
            "Konoha",
            "Suna",
            "Kiri",
            "Kumo"
        ],
        "answer": "Konoha"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the ninja that possesses the ability to control snakes?",
        "options": [
            "Orochimaru",
            "Kabuto Yakushi",
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Jiraiya"
        ],
        "answer": "Orochimaru"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is known for their ability to use the 'Eight Gates' technique?",
        "options": [
            "Might Guy",
            "Kakashi Hatake",
            "Naruto Uzumaki",
            "Rock Lee"
        ],
        "answer": "Might Guy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the powerful taijutsu technique used by Rock Lee?",
        "options": [
            "Eight Gates",
            "Chidori",
            "Rasengan",
            "Shadow Clone Jutsu"
        ],
        "answer": "Eight Gates"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the former member of Team 7 who later becomes a member of the Akatsuki?",
        "options": [
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Orochimaru",
            "Kisame Hoshigaki",
            "Itachi Uchiha"
        ],
        "answer": "Sasuke Uchiha"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the technique that allows a ninja to create clones that can perform jutsu independently?",
        "options": [
            "Shadow Clone Jutsu",
            "Basic Clone Jutsu",
            "Substitution Jutsu",
            "Transformation Jutsu"
        ],
        "answer": "Shadow Clone Jutsu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is known as the 'Yellow Flash'?",
        "options": [
            "Minato Namikaze",
            "Naruto Uzumaki",
            "Kakashi Hatake",
            "Jiraiya"
        ],
        "answer": "Minato Namikaze"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Naruto’s father?",
        "options": [
            "Minato Namikaze",
            "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
            "Tobirama Senju",
            "Hashirama Senju"
        ],
        "answer": "Minato Namikaze"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character possesses the 'Byakugan'?",
        "options": [
            "Hinata Hyuga",
            "Sakura Haruno",
            "Tenten",
            "Temari"
        ],
        "answer": "Hinata Hyuga"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the technique used by the Uchiha clan that allows them to copy other jutsu?",
        "options": [
            "Sharingan",
            "Rinnegan",
            "Byakugan",
            "Kekkei Genkai"
        ],
        "answer": "Sharingan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the leader of Team 10?",
        "options": [
            "Asuma Sarutobi",
            "Kurenai Yuhi",
            "Kakashi Hatake",
            "Iruka Umino"
        ],
        "answer": "Asuma Sarutobi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the forbidden jutsu that involves the resurrection of the dead?",
        "options": [
            "Edo Tensei",
            "Rasengan",
            "Chidori",
            "Summoning Jutsu"
        ],
        "answer": "Edo Tensei"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the member of Team 8 known for her tracking abilities?",
        "options": [
            "Kurenai Yuhi",
            "Hinata Hyuga",
            "Shino Aburame",
            "Kiba Inuzuka"
        ],
        "answer": "Shino Aburame"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character has the ability to control and summon toads?",
        "options": [
            "Jiraiya",
            "Naruto Uzumaki",
            "Kakashi Hatake",
            "Orochimaru"
        ],
        "answer": "Jiraiya"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the character known for his ability to control and summon snakes?",
        "options": [
            "Orochimaru",
            "Kabuto Yakushi",
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Zabuza Momochi"
        ],
        "answer": "Orochimaru"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the technique that allows the user to move at incredible speeds and create afterimages?",
        "options": [
            "Body Flicker Jutsu",
            "Shadow Clone Jutsu",
            "Rasengan",
            "Chidori"
        ],
        "answer": "Body Flicker Jutsu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is known for their ability to manipulate shadows?",
        "options": [
            "Shikamaru Nara",
            "Kiba Inuzuka",
            "Neji Hyuga",
            "Choji Akimichi"
        ],
        "answer": "Shikamaru Nara"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the powerful tailed beast sealed within the character Gaara?",
        "options": [
            "Shukaku",
            "Kurama",
            "Gyuki",
            "Kokuo"
        ],
        "answer": "Shukaku"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the leader of the Akatsuki's organization after Pain?",
        "options": [
            "Nagato",
            "Madara Uchiha",
            "Obito Uchiha",
            "Itachi Uchiha"
        ],
        "answer": "Madara Uchiha"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the jutsu that allows the user to control the weather?",
        "options": [
            "Storm Release",
            "Water Style",
            "Wind Style",
            "Lightning Style"
        ],
        "answer": "Storm Release"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which member of the Akatsuki is known for his ability to manipulate and control puppets?",
        "options": [
            "Sasori",
            "Deidara",
            "Hidan",
            "Kisame Hoshigaki"
        ],
        "answer": "Sasori"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Jutsu used by Naruto to communicate with his clones?",
        "options": [
            "Telepathy",
            "Mind Transfer Jutsu",
            "Shadow Clone Jutsu",
            "Mind Reading"
        ],
        "answer": "Shadow Clone Jutsu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is known for having the ability to manipulate sand and is the Kazekage of the Sand Village?",
        "options": [
            "Gaara",
            "Kankuro",
            "Temari",
            "Shukaku"
        ],
        "answer": "Gaara"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the technique used by the character Madara Uchiha to create a giant meteorite?",
        "options": [
            "Meteorite Jutsu",
            "Chibaku Tensei",
            "Rinnegan",
            "Susanoo"
        ],
        "answer": "Chibaku Tensei"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is known as the 'Great Sage' and the teacher of Naruto?",
        "options": [
            "Jiraiya",
            "Tsunade",
            "Orochimaru",
            "Minato Namikaze"
        ],
        "answer": "Jiraiya"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the forbidden jutsu that allows the user to perform a technique known as 'Reanimation'?",
        "options": [
            "Edo Tensei",
            "Rasengan",
            "Amaterasu",
            "Genjutsu"
        ],
        "answer": "Edo Tensei"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is known for their expertise in genjutsu?",
        "options": [
            "Itachi Uchiha",
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Naruto Uzumaki",
            "Kakashi Hatake"
        ],
        "answer": "Itachi Uchiha"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the technique used by the character Danzo Shimura to use other people’s Sharingan?",
        "options": [
            "Kotoamatsukami",
            "Edo Tensei",
            "Shisui’s Technique",
            "Izanagi"
        ],
        "answer": "Izanagi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the powerful ability that allows the user to control the flow of time?",
        "options": [
            "Rinnegan",
            "Eternal Mangekyo Sharingan",
            "Kekkei Genkai",
            "Tenseigan"
        ],
        "answer": "Rinnegan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is known for his use of 'Black Flames' that cannot be extinguished?",
        "options": [
            "Itachi Uchiha",
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Madara Uchiha",
            "Kaguya Otsutsuki"
        ],
        "answer": "Itachi Uchiha"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the village where Naruto grew up?",
        "options": [
            "Konoha",
            "Suna",
            "Kiri",
            "Iwa"
        ],
        "answer": "Konoha"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is known for his mastery of the 'Wind Style' techniques?",
        "options": [
            "Naruto Uzumaki",
            "Temari",
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Kakashi Hatake"
        ],
        "answer": "Naruto Uzumaki"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the character known for his ability to use 'The First Hokage’s Techniques'?",
        "options": [
            "Hashirama Senju",
            "Tobirama Senju",
            "Madara Uchiha",
            "Minato Namikaze"
        ],
        "answer": "Hashirama Senju"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the eye technique that grants the user the ability to use powerful space-time jutsu?",
        "options": [
            "Rinnegan",
            "Sharingan",
            "Byakugan",
            "Tenseigan"
        ],
        "answer": "Rinnegan"
    }
 ]
